Labourer with more than 10 years' experience in farming, factory and construction settings. Excels on small teams in a fast paced environment and works to complete projects quickly and efficiently.

Safety oriented, with an excellent attention to detail.

SKILLS

Valid G Drivers' License with a clean driving record

Working at Heights certified

WHMIS trained

Workplace Health and Safety trained

Sound carpentry skills with a good knowledge of hand and power tools

Strong math and problem-solving skills

Proficient with Microsoft Office applications, Internet navigation, and Emails

EXPERIENCE

Farm Labour

- Operated and maintained tractors, farm and lawn equipment
- Completed tractor motor rebuild and reassembly
- Cleaned and maintained grain bins
- Baled hay and straw

Factory Labour

- Set up and operated injection molding machine to shape plastics
- Met production and scrap targets regularly
- Maintained a safe work environment

Handyman

- Assisted with roof repair and home renovation /construction
- Built and repaired decks
- Performed minor repairs including replacing kitchen and bathroom fixtures
- Assisted with lawn and garden maintenance

WORK HISTORY

Farm Labourer, McAuslan Farms, Petrolia, ON	2002 - present
Handyman, Private Clients, Sarnia and Lambton County, ON	2010 - 2018
Mold Operator, Waterville TG, Petrolia, ON	2013 - 2015
Abatement Technician, Canadian Industrial Specialties, Sarnia, ON	2008 - 2011

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Handyman, Private Clients, Brigden, ON

EDUCATION

Ontario Secondary School Diploma, Petrolia, ON